You know, it hit me this morning that I've been thinking about this book tour all wrong, because I'm not going on a book tour. I'm going on a mission. When you understand and you realize how propagandized we are as a nation and that that's not some made up shit, that is some actualized billion dollar effort that's been going on since the end of World War Two.
You understand that they have identified individuals who are focused on waking people up and taking them out because when the people wake up, they will not allow for what's been done in their name to continue.
And for what's been done to them to continue, you realize that you're not you're not going on tour.
You're going on a mission. I've been so unsettled this morning, and I think it's because I'm waking up to.
Well, first of all, it's the second of the month, but you know, fall is when we release we let go that which is no longer bringing in nutrients we we alleviate ourselves of that which is encumbering us because we know we have to hunker down for that which is coming.
And we know as Ned Stark has always told us winter is coming and I'm heading out on this book tour with a book that is not about pop culture.
It's not about relationships.
It's not about it's not about any frivolities that I've engaged myself in in the past.
What would the ancestors say is literally about what would our ancestors say about where we are?
What type of ancestors are we trying to be for the future?
And that is not a small concept.
That's not a it's not even a linear concept.
And so I'm over here trying to wrap my head around going out on this this road to, you know, share this work with you and and bring these books to you.
And I'm realizing that the reason why I feel like I'm so kind of like unsettled about it is because I'm not going out in the same way that I have gone out before as a comic on tour or doing smart, funny and black on tour.
This is a mission to awaken, to empower, to educate, not just for the sake of it, but for literally our lives.
See you there.
Go to AmandaSales.com for cities and dates.